email-clicks.com 2014-11-08

# Privacy Policy | FEEDGEE email marketing tools

**FEEDGEE PRIVACY GUARANTEE**  
At FEEDGEE we respect and protect the privacy of our customers and those who use our website. The following Privacy Statement provides details about how your personal information is collected and used. This privacy statement applies to the FEEDGEE website, products and services that are located in and limited to the feedgee.com domain.

**Information Collection and Use**  
FEEDGEEis the sole owner of information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. FEEDGEE collects information from our users at several different points on our website.

Our website offers opportunity for visitors to register for promotional and informational mailings, online webinars and resources, and for assistance in evaluating our software and services. This registration form is linked to FEEDGEE's mailing lists and requires users to give contact information (such as name and email address). We use this contact information to send users information about FEEDGEE project and its products and services if requested or necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings at any time (see the choice/opt-out section below). Providing accurate personal, public, and contact information and agreeing with terms and conditions of FEEDGEE sites (website) are required.

Registering on the website you confirm your mutual consent to create your account on the website and subscribe your email address used for registration for the website newsletter and your account status alerts.

When completing your account details you provide accurate information e.g. company or project name, contact information (country, address, telephone number).

**Public account information**  
Some information saved in account details - the company / organization / project name (if not, the name and family name), a web site, country, address and subscribers support phone is considered as public account information, free access to which should be provided to owners of email-addresses and / or other parties whose personal data is stored in your account.

**Sharing and Usage**  
We will never share, sell, or rent your personal information with third parties for their promotional use. Occasionally, we enter into contracts with third parties so that they can assist us in servicing you (for example, providing customer service). The contracts prohibit them from using any of your personal information for their own purposes, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of the information we provide to them. Lastly, we may disclose or report personal information in limited circumstances where we believe in good faith that disclosure is required under the law. For example, we may be required to disclose personal and public information to cooperate with regulators or law enforcement authorities, to comply with a legal process such as court order, subpoena, search warrant, law enforcement request or to disclose public information to the owners of email addresses and the owners of personal data stored in your account disclosure requests, to requests of individuals, organizations and services whose work, policy or rules may be violated by operations made in your account on the website.

**Links**  
Site provides links to third-party websites, such as those of our business partners and advertisers. While on these sites, FEEDGEE or its partners may collect information about you. Because FEEDGEE does not control the information policies or practices of these third parties, you should review their privacy policies to learn more about how they collect and use personally identifiable information.

**Security**  
We take every precaution to protect the confidentiality and security of your personal information by using industry-recognized security safeguards such as firewalls, coupled with carefully developed security procedures to protect your information from loss, misuse or unauthorized alteration.

FEEDGEE takes care to reinforce the importance of our website visitors' security and privacy among our employees. Our employees are trained and required to safeguard your information and, using physical, electronic and procedural safeguards, we restrict access to personal information to those employees and agents for business purposes only. Additionally, we use internal and external resources to review the adequacy of our security procedures.

**Choice/Opt-out**  
FEEDGEE provides users the opportunity to opt-in, opt-out via a link in the footer of most email messages. These options are made available when you sign-up for our email lists and in email messages delivered from us. Alternatively, you may email us at support@feedgee.com.

Some communications (e.g. important account notifications) are necessary for all FEEDGEE customers. You must cancel your FEEDGEE account to unsubscribe from these communications. To cancel your FEEDGEE account, please email us at support@feedgee.com.

**Notification of Changes**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on the FEEDGEE Website. So our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.
